<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Woodpeckers</title><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Woodpeckers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsserver/azuredevopsserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsserver/azuredevopsserver/</guid><description>Azure DevOps Server # Azure DevOps Server previously known as Team Foundation Server (commonly abbreviated to TFS) is a Microsoft product that provides below capabilities.
Requirements management Project management Source code management Automated builds Testing Release management Reporting It covers the entire application lifecycle, and enables DevOps capabilities. ADO in Roche Diagnostics supports mainly with software development process by hosting Source control repository, Document Storage, Reporting, building and testing of software.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsserver/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsserver/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsservice/agentpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsservice/agentpool/</guid><description>Agent Pool # Agent: Agent is a service which runs on a machine where we can build, deploy software using Azure Pipelines
Two types of agents: # Microsoft-Hosted Agents Self-hosted agents Microsoft-hosted agents: Microsoft-hosted agents that run Windows and Linux images are provisioned on Azure general purpose virtual machines with a 2 core CPU, 7 GB of RAM, and 14 GB of SSD disk space.
Self-hosted agents: An agent that is hosted in our local network machine with high and customized software configuration.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsservice/azuredevopsservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsservice/azuredevopsservice/</guid><description>Azure DevOps Services # Azure DevOps is a Microsoft product that provides developer services for allowing teams to plan work, collaborate on code development, and build and deploy applications. Azure DevOps supports a collaborative culture and set of processes that bring together developers, project managers, and contributors to develop software. It allows organizations to create and improve products at a faster pace than they can with traditional software development approaches.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsservice/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/azuredevopsservice/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/dsc/dsc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/dsc/dsc/</guid><description>DSC # Management platform provided by the Microsoft, also known as a powershell feature. DSC provides a set of Power Shell language extensions and cmdlets. The main idea is to provide a method for maintaining consistent configuration across computers or devices.Using central DSC server, projects can store OS configuration and use it several times across builds.Mainly used for configuration, deployment and management of systems and configuration.
Woodpeckers team is supplying a complete solution for the business partners who would like to enhance their DSC practice.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/dsc/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/dsc/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/ear/ear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/ear/ear/</guid><description>Enterprise Architect # Sparx Systems Enterprise Architect is a visual modeling and design tool based on the OMG UML. The platform supports: the design and construction of software systems; modeling business processes; and modeling industry based domains.
Why use EAR? # 1.Fast Intuitive Modeling &amp;amp; Design
2.Manage complex information
3.Flexible and rich
4.Model, manage and trace
5.Load extremely large models in seconds 6.Collaborate effectively globally
How to use EAR?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/ear/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/ear/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/github/github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/github/github/</guid><description>GitHub Enterprise Cloud # GitHub Enterprise is a software development and version control using Git. It offers the distributed version control and source code management functionality of Git, plus its own features.
Why use GitHub? # 1.Setting up secure workflows
2.Understanding the GitHub Flow
3.Reviewing and discussing work
4.Planning and tracking work
5.Automating with GitHub Actions
6.Integrating apps with GitHub
7.Using the GitHub API
How to get Read Access # Reader access to GitHub can be provided to your team by subscribing to the group GLOAZUGHAdmin_ReadOnly.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/github/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/github/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/hyperv/hyperv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/hyperv/hyperv/</guid><description>Hyper-V # Hyper-V cluster is a set of several similar Hyper-V servers (called nodes), which can be specifically configured to work together, so that one node can take the load (VMs, services, processes) if another one goes down or if there is a disaster. Customers can request for virtual machines to consume in CI/CD pipelines. We provide a dedicated cluster to manage virtual machines by the team or we manage virtual machines in a shared cluster for the team.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/hyperv/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/hyperv/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/innersource/innersource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/innersource/innersource/</guid><description>Innersource within Roche # What is Open Source? # Open source projects are accessible to everyone. Anyone can use these open source softwares. They can also view, modify, and distribute a project for any purpose—as enforced by open source licenses. Similarly, anyone can help build open source software. In general, projects are developed by a community of distributed contributors who share code, feedback, bug reports, and more.
What is innersource?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/innersource/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/innersource/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/proget/proget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/proget/proget/</guid><description>Proget # ProGet helps you package applications and components so you can ensure your software is built only once, and then deployed consistently across environments. This means everyone can be certain that what goes to production is exactly what was built and tested. Third-party packages (such as NuGet, npm, PowerShell, and Chocolatey) and Docker containers are also supported, allowing you to enforce quality standards, monitor for open-source licenses, and scan for vulnerabilities across all packages, much earlier in the development cycle.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/proget/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/proget/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/sonarqube/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/sonarqube/readme/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/sonarqube/sonarqube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodpeckers-wiki.roche.com/docs/sonarqube/sonarqube/</guid><description>Sonarqube # SonarQube provides automated capabilities for continuous inspection of code, detect bugs, code smells and security vulnerabilities on 20+ programming languages, with the historical data and many features it gives enormous possibilities for the project to improve their code.
Main Purpose # Used across different projects, where the code quality can be easily measured and self maintained. SonarQube helps projects to understand the quality of their software and ensures the transparency of code.</description></item></channel></rss>